

### **ABOUT ME**

A diligent and enthusiastic frontend focused fullstack developer with 1 year of working experience.

As an individual I am friendly and approachable person with experience of multiple cultures that can adapt in many different social groups.

My main passion lays within the IT domain and always curious to learn more. Other passions includes cooking, walks in nature and games.

# WEBSITE & SOCIAL LINKS

LinkedIn

<u>linkedin.com/in/alexander-risteski-seiya</u>

GitHub github.com/Kanzaki404

Portfolio

alexander-risteski-seiya.com

#### **LANGUAGES**

ENGLISH Fluent

NORTH MACEDONIAN

SWEDISH

Proficient

**JAPANESE** 

Proficient

SERBO-CROATIAN
Conversational

## ALEXANDER RISTESKI SEIYA

Jr. Developer

#### Alexander.Risteski@protonmail.com ■

073 755 20 22

Västanvindsgatan 6A, Göteborg

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Stratsys

Göteborg Sep 2021 - Present

**Ericsson** 

Göteborg Oct 2020 - May 2021

#### Hello World!

Växjö Mar 2018 - Jun 2018

#### Arrow Value Recovery Sweden AB

Växjö Jun 2017 - Jul 2017

#### Jr Developer Trainee (fullstack)

- Creating and updating micro-frontends in vue3.
- · Writing unit tests with jest.
- Implementing accessibility support for screen readers and tested using NVDA program.
- Agile processes with tools such as Jira, Git and Azure.
- Learning .Net framework and engaging in bug fixes

#### Frontend Developer Intern

- Creation of wireframe, mockup and implementation of frontend as well as backend with database.
- Thesis work at Ericsson was conducted through a task to create a mobile version of an already existing web/ browser app using React Native

#### **Programming Instructor**

 My task included teaching programming concepts using a program called Scratch and engage the students by building simple games.

#### Material Handler

 Inspecting, evaluating and registering of used electronic devices such as portable/stationary computers and other office related devices.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **EC Utbildning**

Göteborg Sep 2019 - May 2021

#### **Linnaeus University**

Växjö

Sep 2016 - Jun 2019

#### Frontend Developer

- Main topics were fundamentals of web development, front end frameworks, UX/UI, Agile work and surface level backend/database courses.
- The education includes 6 month period of internship with an aim to gain work experience upon graduation.

#### **Network Security Program**

- Areas of focus were network/server administration, network security and cryptography.
- The program also included courses within software development such as data structures, software testing and database theories.

#### **SKILLS**

#### Frontend

HTML/CSS
JavaScript
TypeScript
Vue 2&3
Jest
React
React Native
Angular

#### Backend

NodeJS ASP.Net MVC

#### Databases

MongoDB
SQL

UX/UI
Figma
Photoshop

#### **Work Methodologies**

Agile Scrum Kanban